<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Dayfiles Blog</title>
    <link>https://dayfiles.com/blog</link>
    <description>Daily workflow guides for Everyday Image Studio and PDF Toolkit.</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Everyday Image Studio Chrome Extension Is Now Live on Product Hunt]]></title>
      <link>https://dayfiles.com/blog/product-hunt-launch-everyday-image-studio</link>
      <guid>https://dayfiles.com/blog/product-hunt-launch-everyday-image-studio</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[Dayfiles launched the Everyday Image Studio Chrome Extension on Product Hunt, with a focused browser editing workflow and more features already on the roadmap.]]></description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[From Accra to Berlin: A Student Visa Application Story Powered by Dayfiles]]></title>
      <link>https://dayfiles.com/blog/student-visa-application-story</link>
      <guid>https://dayfiles.com/blog/student-visa-application-story</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[A practical story of how one student preparing for studies in Germany used Dayfiles tools to organize documents, fix image assets, and submit a clean visa-ready application package.]]></description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Why Dayfiles Blog Uses Google Ads to Keep Practical Guides Free]]></title>
      <link>https://dayfiles.com/blog/google-ads-content-support</link>
      <guid>https://dayfiles.com/blog/google-ads-content-support</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[A transparent explanation of how Dayfiles uses relevant Google Ads to support free workflow content for students, job applicants, and small teams.]]></description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[PDF Toolkit Operations Checklist for Reliable Document Delivery]]></title>
      <link>https://dayfiles.com/blog/pdf-operations-checklist</link>
      <guid>https://dayfiles.com/blog/pdf-operations-checklist</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[Use this checklist to standardize PDF conversion, compression, and delivery with fewer errors and faster approvals.]]></description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Everyday Image Studio Workflow Playbook for Daily Creative Operations]]></title>
      <link>https://dayfiles.com/blog/eis-workflow-playbook</link>
      <guid>https://dayfiles.com/blog/eis-workflow-playbook</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[A practical guide for teams that need faster image turnaround, consistent quality, and cleaner handoffs using Everyday Image Studio.]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
